Finding Aid for Faculty and Staff Assistance Program (University of Michigan) records, 1973-1996
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Initiative on Alcohol and Other Drugs
  - Phase II Activity
    - Department of Public Safety-Housing Security (Box 7)
    - Emergency Room Data (Box 7)
    - Employee Rehab and Claims Control (Box 7)
    - FASAP (Box 7)
    - Greek System (Box 7)
    - Hospital Security Services (Box 7)
    - Housing (Box 7)
    - Liquor Licenses (Box 7)
    - Managed Care Program (Box 7)
    - Medical Procedures Unit (Box 7)
    - Michigan League (Box 7)
    - Michigan Union (Box 7)
    - Michigan Union Student Organizations (Box 7)
    - Office of Student Affairs (Box 7)
    - Personnel-Administrative Services (Box 7)
    - Personnel-Medical Campus (Box 7)
    - Psychiatry (Box 7)
    - Report: Program Summary, Planning, Major Findings, Preliminary Recommendations 1994 (Box 7)
    - Sexual Assault and Prevention Center (SAPAC) (Box 7)
    - Student Counseling Services (Box 7)
    - Transportation Services (Box 7)
    - University Health Services (Box 7)
  - Topical Files
    - Insurance Issues (Box 7)
    - Legal Issues (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous Information (Box 7)
    - Self-Help Groups (Box 7)
Related Material
For additional records on the topic of substance abuse at the University of Michigan, the researcher should consult the following related record groups, available at the Bentley Historical Library:
University of Michigan. Vice President for Student Services.
University of Michigan. Vice Provost for Medical Affairs